

ADRI TELLEZ DIGITAL DESIGNER

I'm a graphic designer oriented to web and mobile product design. I like to create enjoyable and functional experiences, in some cases I like to use illustration as a graphic resource. I can contribute not only to design but also in templating process of a website.

EDUCATION

INSTITUTION

CUN (Corporación Unificada Nacional)

DEGREE: PROFESSIONAL TECHNICIAN IN GRAPHIC DESIGN

COURSES:

UX/UI Design

Coderhouse

After effects - Character animation

Microanimations

Domestika

Introdution to responsive web development with HTML and CSS

Domestika

Advanced web development techniques

HTML5 and CSS3

Domestika

WORK EXPERIENCE

2020 - Present UX UI Designer

DDB Latina Puerto Rico

Working alongside developers building web apps, e-commerce and websites 2017 - 2020 UI Designer

El Pixel

Contributed in the UI design process

2016 - 2017 Web/Digital Designer

Socialive Argentina

Landing pages, microsites, apps, and social media design.

2015-2016 Independent Freelance Web/Digital Designer

Participated in several clients projects, wich involved web design, illustration, editorial design and packaging design.

2010 - 2015 Graphic Designer

I worked in digital print and offset art, proffesional printer operations, as well as print and cut plotter, photographic retouch and layouting.

2009 -2010 Internship

SKILLS AND KNOWLEDGE

ILUSTRATOR PHOTOSHOP ADOBE XD AFTER EFFECTS PREMIER INVISION HTML5 CSS3

ACCESIBILITY USABILITY CARD SORTING STYLE GUIDE MOBILE FIRST USERFLOW

DESIGN PATTERNS UX/UI DESIGN MARVEL APP

GRAPHIC TOOLS







WEB TOOLS





UX/UI TOOLS







Operative systems: Windows, OSX.

Languages:

Spanish: Native

English: Intemediate

Mercedes, Buenos Aires

adri077@gmail.com



